Born of cold and Winter air And mountain rain combining,
寒冷的夜晚伴随着山雨她出生了
This icy force both foul and fair.
不畏严寒的肆虐
Has a frozen heart worth mining.
冰封的心等待着挖掘
Cut through the heart, Cold and Clear.
寒冷剔透的心
Strike for love And Strike for fear.
为了爱而不畏恐惧
See the beauty Sharp and Sheer.
一双善于发现美丽的眼睛
Split the ice apart.
打破寒冰结境
And break the frozen heart.
融化冰封之心
Hup! Ho! Watch your step! Let it go!
全神贯注!放手去爱!
Beautiful! Powerful!
美丽又动人!
Dangerous! Cold!
寒冷又危险!
Ice has a magic Can't be controlled.
冰的魔法无法被掌控
Stronger than one, Stronger than ten.
不害怕一个人 也不害怕十个人
Stronger than a hundred men!
一百个人也不放在眼里
Born of cold and winter air And mountain rain combining.
寒冷的夜晚伴随着山雨她出生了
This icy force both Foul and Fair.
不畏严寒的肆虐
Has a frozen heart worth mining.
冰封的心等待着挖掘
Cut through the heart, Cold and Clear.
寒冷剔透的心
Strike for love and strike for fear.
为了爱而不畏恐惧
There's beauty and there's Danger here.
美丽与危险共存
Split the ice apart!
打破寒冰结境
Beware the frozen heart.
融化冰封之心
Come on, Sven!
快来呀 斯文!
Elsa. Psst
埃尔莎
Elsa!
埃尔莎!
Wake up. Wake up. Wake up.
快醒来
Anna, go back to sleep.
安娜 回你的床上去
I just can't. The sky's awake, so I'm awake,
我不能 天是醒的 所以我也是醒的
so we have to play.
我们来玩游戏吧
...Go play by yourself.
和自己玩去吧
Do you want to build a snowman?
你想堆雪人吗?
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
来吧 来吧 来吧
Do the magic! Do the magic!
来点魔法! 来点魔法!
Ready? Uhhm...
准备好了没?
This is amazing!
太神奇啦!
Watch this!
看好了!
Hi, I'm Olaf and I like warm hugs.
嘿 我是喜欢温暖拥抱的雪宝
I love you, Olaf.
我爱你 雪宝
Al'right. Catch me! - Gotcha!
好 接住我! -接住啦!
Again! Wait!
再来一次! -等下!
Slow down!
慢一点!
Anna!
安娜!
Anna?
安娜?
Mama! Papa!
妈!爸爸!
You Ok, Anna. I Got you.
没事的 安娜 我陪着你
Elsa, what have you done? This is getting out of hand!
埃尔莎 你做了什么?你又乱用魔法了!
It was an accident. I'm sorry, Anna.
这是个意外 对不起 安娜
- She's ice cold. - I know where we have to go.
她冰冷的 -我知道我们得去哪
Ice?
冰?
Faster, Sven!
快点 斯文!
Sven!
斯文!
Please... Help!
请帮帮我们!
My daughter!
救救我们的女儿!
He is the King!
他是国王!
Trolls...?
巨魔?
Shush. I'm trying to listen.
嘘 我要听听发生了什么
Cuties. I'm gonna keep you.
小可爱们 我要留下你们
Your Majesty!
陛下!
Born with the powers or cursed?
与生俱来的力量还是诅咒?
Born. And they're getting stronger.
生下来就有的 而且越来越强大
You are lucky it wasn't her heart.
好在没有击中她的心
The heart is not so easily changed,
击中心的话就没那么容易改变了
But the head can be persuaded.
击中头的话还有办法
Do what you must.
做你必须做的
I recommend we remove all magic,
我建议我们消除她身上所有的魔力
even memories of magic to be safe...
为了安全连着这段记忆也一起
But don't worry, I'll leave the fun.
别担心 我会留下快乐的记忆
She will be okay.
她会没事的
But she won't remember I have powers?
她会忘记我有的魔力?
- It's for the best. - Listen to me, Elsa,
这样是最好的 -听着 埃尔莎
your power will only grow.
你的魔力只会越来越强大
There is beauty in it...
你会发现它的美好
But also great danger.
同时也伴随着危险
You must learn to control it.
你一定要学会控制它
Fear will be your enemy.
恐惧会成为你的敌人
No. We'll protect her. She can learn to control it. I'm sure.
不 我们会保护她 她能做到的 相信我
Until then,
在这之前
we'll lock the gates. We'll reduce the staff.
我们会锁上大门 减少仆人
We will limit her contact with people
限制她与人的交往
and keep her powers hidden from everyone...
让她的魔力不被人所知
including Anna.
包括安娜
Elsa?
埃尔莎?
Do you want to build a snowman?
你想堆雪人吗?
Come on let's go and play.
来吧我们一起来玩吧
I never see you anymore. Come out the door.
好久没见到你了 出来吧
It's like you've gone away.
你就像消失了一样
We used to be best buddies.
我们曾是最好的玩伴
And now we're not. I wish you would tell me why.
现在却变了 你能告诉我原因吗
Do you want to build a snowman?
你想堆雪人吗?
It doesn't have to be a snowman.
玩什么都可以呀
Go away, Anna.
离我远点 安娜
...Okay bye.
好吧 拜
The gloves will help. See...
带上手套就没事了 看到了吗...
- Conceal it. - Don't feel it.
隐藏它 -别去感受
Don't let it show.
别显现出来
Do you want to build a snowman?
你想堆雪人吗?
Or ride our bike around the hall?
还是绕着走廊骑自行车?
I think some company is overdue...
我觉得这里的同伴太少了..
I've started talking to the pictures on the walls.
我开始和墙上的画像讲话
Hang in there, Joan.
坚持住 琼
It gets a little lonely all these empty rooms.
这些空房子让人觉得有些寂寞
Just watching the hours tick by.
凝视着时间滴答滴答
I'm scared. It's getting stronger.
我很害怕 它变的越来越强大
Getting upset only makes it worse.
不安只会让情况变糟
Calm down.
冷静下来
No. Don't touch me. Please. I don't want to hurt you.
别碰我 我怕伤害了你
See you in two weeks.
两周后再见
- Do you have to go? - You'll be fine, Elsa.
你要走了吗? -你会没事的 埃尔莎
Elsa?
埃尔莎?
Please, I know you're in there.
请回答我 我知道你在里面
People are asking where you've been,
人们都在找你
They say have courage and I'm trying to...
他们说要有勇气 而我在尝试
I'm right out here for you. Just let me in.
我在外面等你 让我进来吧
We only have each other.
我们只拥有彼此了
It's just you and me.
只有你和我
What are we gonna do?
我们该怎么办?
Do you want to build a snowman?
你想堆雪人吗?
三年后
Welcome to Arendelle! Thank you, Sir!
欢迎来到安瑞戴尔 谢谢你!
Watch your Steps please. The Gates Will opening Soon.
注意脚下 大门马上要打开了
Why do I have to wear this?
我一定要穿这个吗?
Because the Queen has come of age.
因为女王的时代已经来临了
It's Coronation Day!
今天是加冕日!
That's not my fault.
跟我有什么关系
- What do you want, Sven? - Give me a snack!
你想要什么 斯文? -给我点吃的!
What's the magic word? Please!
魔法单词是什么? 请!
A..a... a... a! Share!
A..a....a....a! 分享!
I can't believe they're finally opening up the gates!
不敢相信他们终于打开那些门了
And for a whole day!
而且打开一整天哦!
Faster, Persi!
快 珀西!
Ah, Arendelle, our most mysterious trade partner.
安瑞戴尔 我们最神秘的交易拍档
Open those gates so I may unlock your secrets
打开那些门我就可以洞悉你的秘密
and exploit your riches.
挖掘你的财富
...Did I just say that out loud?
我刚说的很大声吗?
Oh, me sore eyes can't wait to.
我已经等不急想看看
See the Queen and the Princess.
女王跟公主了
I bet they're absolutely lovely.
我打赌她们一定可爱极了
I bet they are beautiful.
她们一定美级了
Princess Anna...?
安娜公主?
...Huh? Yeah?
恩?
- Sorry to wake you, ma'am but... - No, no, no. You didn't.
抱歉要叫醒你 -没事的
I've been up for hours.
我起床几个小时了
Who is it?
谁啊?
It's still me, ma'am. The gates will open soon.
还是我 门马上就要开了
Time to get ready. Of course!
要准备好了! -当然了!
Ready for what?
准备什么?
Your sister's coronation, ma'am.
你姐姐的加冕礼
My sister's cor-neration...
我姐姐的加冕...
It's coronation day!
今天是加冕日!
加冕日!
The window is open! So's that door!
窗户是开的!门也是!
I didn't know they did that anymore.
他们已经做了如此多的准备
Who knew we owned 8000 salad plates...?
谁知道我们会有八千盘色拉?
For years I have roamed these empty halls.
多年以来我一直徘徊在这些空荡荡的大厅里
Why have a ballroom with no balls?
我们的舞厅里为什么没有舞会?
Finally, they're opening up the gates!
终于 他们打开那些门!
There'll be actual real live people
会有真正的人们到来
It'll be totally strange.
肯定会很奇妙
But wow am I so ready for this change!
但我已经做好准备了!
For the first time in forever,
这将是第一次
There'll be music, there'll be light.
奏响音乐 点亮灯光
For the first time in forever,
而我也将终于
I'll be dancing through the night.
彻夜跳舞
Don't know if I'm elated or gassy,
我是否太高兴得意了一点
But I'm somewhere in that zone.
但我就是这么开心
'Cause for the first time in forever,
这将是第一次
I won't be alone. I can't wait to meet everyone...
我不再是一个人 我等不急见到每一个人
What if I meet "the one"?
如果我遇见"他"怎么办?
Tonight, imagine me gown and all.
想象一下 今晚盛装出席的我
Fetchingly draped against the wall.
穿着最迷人的礼服靠着墙
The picture of sophisticated Grace.
美丽而优雅的形象
I suddenly see him standing there,
我突然见到了伫立一旁的他
a beautiful stranger tall and fair.
一个美丽的陌生人 高大而白皙
I wanna stuff some chocolate in my face!
我想要在脸上涂一些巧克力!
But then we laugh and talk all evening,
然后我们畅谈欢笑整晚
Which is totally bizarre.
肯定会很奇妙
Nothing like the life I've led so far.
与我之前的生活迥然不同
For the first time in forever,
这将是第一次
There'll be magic, There'll be fun.
充满了魔力 充满了欢乐
For the first time in forever,
这将是第一次
I could be noticed by someone.
我能被他人注视
And I know it is totally crazy.
我知道这肯定会很疯狂
To dream I'd find romance.
梦到我找到了罗曼蒂克
But for the first time in forever,
这将是第一次
At least I've got a chance!
至少我有机会!
Don't let them in. Don't let them see.
别让别人知道 别让别人看到
Be the good girl You always have to be.
你是个好姑娘 你必须一直是
Conceal. Don't feel.
要隐藏 不要感受
Put on a show.
好好表现自己
Make one wrong move and everyone will know.
一失足而天下人皆知
But it's only for today.
仅此一天
It's only for today! It's agony to wait.
仅此一天!等的心碎
It's agony to wait.
等待让人心碎
Tell the guards to open up the...
快让守卫们把大门...
The gate!
打开!
For the first time in forever.
这将是第一次
Don't let them in don't let them see
别让别人知道 别让别人看到
I'm getting what I'm dreaming of.
我梦寐以求的时刻终于要来临
Be the good girl you always have to be.
你是个好姑娘 你必须一直是
A chance to change my Only world.
一个改变我个人世界的机会
Conceal. Conceal. Don't feel.
隐藏 隐藏 不要感受
- A chance to find true love - Don't See, Don't Feel, Don't Let them know.
找到真爱的机会 -别看 别感受 别让人们知道了
I know it all ends tomorrow,
我知道明天就会结束
So it has to be today!
所以一定要在今天!
'Cause for the first time in forever...
因为这将是第一次...
For the first time in forever!
这将是第一次!
Nothing's in my way!
没有什么能阻止我!
Hey! I'm so sorry. Are you hurt?
嘿 对不起 你受伤了吗?
Hey!
嘿!
I-ya, no. No. I'm okay. Are you sure?
我 我没事 -真的吗?
Yeah, I just wasn't looking where I was going.
我刚刚没有看路
- But I'm great, actually. - Oh, thank goodness.
我没事的 -谢天谢地
Oh... Umm...
哦...嗯..
Prince Hans of the Southern Isles.
我是南部小岛的汉斯王子
Princess Anna of Arendelle. Princess...?
我是安瑞戴尔的安娜公主 -公主?
My Lady.
尊敬的公主
Hi... again.
嗨
Oh boy.
噢
Ha. This is awkward. Not you're awkward,
这有点尴尬 你不需要觉得尴尬
but just because we're...I'm awkward.
但我们确实..至少我这样觉得
You're gorgeous. Wait, what?
你很漂亮 -等等 什么?
I'd like to formally apologize for
我正式的为我
hitting the Princess of Arendelle with my horse...
不小心骑马撞上了美丽的安瑞戴尔公主以及
And for every moment after.
之后我所有的举措而抱歉
No. No-no. It's fine. I'm not THAT Princess.
没关系的 我不是“那种”公主
I mean, if you'd hit my sister Elsa, that would be...
如果你撞到的是我姐姐埃尔莎 她大概会...
'Cuz, you know...
你知道的...
Hello.
你好
But, lucky you, it's-it's just me.
还好你撞到的是我
Just you?
还好?
...The bells. The coronation.
铃声 是加冕礼
I... I...
我..
I better go. I have to...I better go.
我要走了
Bye!
再见!
Your Majesty, The gloves.
陛下 手套
(formal, in Old Norse) Sehm hon hell drr in-um hell-gum Ayg-num Ok
[古挪威语的官方语言]...一些赞颂词...
krund ee thes-um hellgah Stahth, ehk teh frahm fur-ear Uthear...
...Queen Elsa of Arendelle.
安瑞戴尔女王埃尔莎
Queen Elsa of Arendelle.
Princess Anna of Arendelle!
安瑞戴尔公主安娜
Here? Are you sure? I do not think I suppose to...Okay.
这么近?你确定吗?我不觉得我应该..好吧
Hi.
嗨
Hi me...? Oh. Um. Hi.
跟我打招呼吗?噢 嗨
You look beautiful...Thank you.
你很漂亮 -谢谢
You look beautifuller. I mean, not Fuller.
你更漂亮一些 不是说你是清洗工
You don't look Fuller, but more beautiful.
你不像清洗工 你更漂亮一些
Thank you.
谢谢
So, this is what a party looks like?
派对就是这样的吗?
It's warmer than I thought.
比我想象的要暖和一些
And what is that amazing smell?
这是什么好味道?
... Chocolate.
巧克力
Your Majesty. The Duke of Weaseltown.
女王陛下 这是鼬鼠城的公爵
Weselton. The Duke of Weselton..
威士顿 威士顿的公爵..
Your Majesty,
陛下
As your closest partner in trade,
作为您最亲密的交易拍档
It seems only fitting that I offer you.
看来我邀请你跳第一支舞
Your first dance as Queen.
是再适合不过了
Thank you... Only I don't dance.
谢谢..但我不会跳舞
But my sister does.
但我妹妹会
Lucky you...Oh, I don't think...
你真幸运 -我不觉得...
If you swoon, let me know, I'll catch you.
要晕倒的时候让我知道 我会接着你
Sorry.
不好意思
Like an agile peacock...
像只灵活的孔雀
Speaking of, so great to have the gates open.
说到这个 能打开城门真是太好了
Why did they shut them in the first place?
一开始干嘛要关上呢?
Do you know the reason? Hmm?
你知道原因吗?
No. No...
不知道
Oh, all right. Hang on.
好吧 我们继续
They don't call me "the little dipper" for nothing.
他们叫我"小北斗星"可不是乱叫的
Like a chicken...with the face of a monkey... I fly.
就像一只 长了猴子脸的鸡 我飞
Let me know when you're ready for another round, M'Lady.
准备好下一次的话告诉我 我的女士
Well, he was sprightly.
他真是活跃
Especially for a man in heels.
对于一位穿了高跟鞋的男士的确是的
Are you okay? I've never been better.
你还好吗? -不能再好了
This is so nice.
那就好
I wish it could be like this all the time.
能永远这样就好了
Me too...
我也觉得...
But it can't.
但是不行
Why not? If...It just can't.
为什么不行? -就是..不行
Excuse me for a minute.
我离开一下
Glad I caught you. Hans!
很高兴接住你 -汉斯!
I often had the whole parlor to myself to slide...Oops. Sorry.
整个客厅里通常只有我一个人玩..哦 不好意思
... Your physique helps I'm sure too.
你的体格起到作用了 我也很肯定
What's this? I was born with it,
这是什么? -生下来就有的
Although I dreamt I was kissed by a troll.
我梦见我被一个巨魔亲过
I like it.
我喜欢
Yeah, The whole thing! You got it.
是的 整件事 你了解了!
Okay wait, wait. So you have how many brothers?
等着 你有多少个兄弟?
Twelve older brothers.
十二个哥哥
Three of them pretended I was invisible...
有三个认为我是不存在的
literally... for two years.
大概 有两年了吧
- That's horrible. - It's what brothers do.
太可怕了 -哥哥就是这样的人
... And sisters.
姐姐也是
Elsa and I were really close when we were little.
我跟埃尔莎在小时候非常的亲密
But then, one day she just shut me out, and...
但有一天 她突然把我关在门外
And I never knew why.
直到现在我还不知道为什么
I would never shut you out.
我永远不会把你关在门外
Okay, can I just say something crazy?
我能说一件疯狂的事吗?
I love crazy.
我爱疯狂
All my life has been a series of doors in my face.
我的一生被关上了很多扇门
And then suddenly I bump into you.
直到我遇见了你
I was thinking the same thing, because like...
我跟你想的一样 因为...
I've been searching my whole life to find my own place.
这一生我一直在寻找归宿
And maybe it's the party talking,
大概是派对上的闲聊
Or the chocolate fondue.
也可能是巧克力干酪
But with you...
但是遇见了你...
I found my place.
我找到了归宿
I see your face.
注视着你的面容
And it's nothing like I've ever known before.
给了我与众不同的感觉
Love is an open... door!
爱情是一扇敞开的门!
Love is an open... door...Door...
爱情是一扇敞开的门
Love is an open... door...
With you! With you!
和你!和你!
Love is an open door.
爱情是一扇敞开的门
I mean it's crazy. What?
我说这很疯狂 -什么?
We finish each other's...Sandwiches!
我们吃了彼此的..."三明治"!
That's what I was gonna say!
我也想这样说!
I've never met someone...Who thinks so much like me.
我从没见过如此理解我的人
Jinx... jinx again.
巧合...多巧!
Our Mental Synchronization Can have but one explanation,
我们的想法如此一致只有一个解释
You and I were just meant to be.
你我注定要
Say goodbye.
告别
To the pain of the past.
过去的痛苦
We don't have to feel it anymore!
再也不用忍受了!
Love is an open... door!
爱情是一扇敞开的门!
Love is an open door!
Life can be so much more...with you! With you!
与你在一起的生活能更充实!
Love is an open... door.
爱情是一扇敞开的门
Can I say something crazy...?
我能说一些疯狂的事吗?
Will you marry me?
你愿意嫁给我吗?
Can I just say something even crazier?
我能说更疯狂的事吗?
Yes.
我愿意
Oops! Pardon. Sorry. Can we just get around you there?
不好意思 能借过一下吗?
Thank you. Oh, there she is.
谢谢 她在这里
Elsa! I mean... Queen...
埃尔莎! 我是说..女王
Me again. May I present,
我又来了 我向您介绍
Prince Hans of the Southern Isles.
南部小岛的汉斯王子
Your Majesty.
尊敬的女王
We would like...your blessing...
希望您能祝福我们的
of... our marriage!
婚姻
Marriage...? Yes!
婚姻? -是的!
I'm sorry, I'm confused.
不好意思 我有点困惑
Well, We haven't worked out all the details ourselves.
好吧 我们还没想好所有的细节
We'll need a few days to plan the ceremony.
我们需要几天的时间来计划庆典
Of course we'll have soup,
当然要有鲜汤
roast, and ice cream and then...
烤肉 冰淇淋还有...
Wait. Would we live here?
等下 我们可以住在这里吗?
Here? Absolutely!
这里? 当然!
Anna...
安娜...
Oh, we can invite all twelve of your brothers to stay with us...
也可以把你的十二个哥哥都请来住...
What? No, no, no, no, no.
什么?那可不行
Of course we have the room. I don't know. Some of them must...
虽然我们有足够的房间 但是 他们一定...
Wait. Slow down.
别说了
No one's brothers are staying here.
没有一个哥哥会住在这里
No one is getting married.
没有人可以结婚
Wait, what?
什么?
May I talk to you, please. Alone.
能跟你单独说说吗?
No. Whatever you have to say, you...
不 无论你想说什么..
you can say to both of us.
你跟我们两人一起说
Fine. You can't marry a man you just met.
好吧 你不能嫁给一个你才刚见面的人
You Can if it's true love.
如果是真爱的话就可以
Anna, what do you know about true love?
安娜 你知道什么是真爱?
More than you. All you know is how to shut people out.
比你要清楚 你只会把人关在门外
You asked for my blessing, but my answer is no.
你请求我的祝福 我的答案是不可以
Now, Excuse me.
现在 不好意思
Your Majesty, if I may ease your...
陛下 请冷静...
No, you may not. And I-I think you should go.
不行 你该走了
The party is over. Close the gates.
派对结束了 把门关上
Yes, Your Majesty.
遵命 尊敬的女王
What? Elsa, no. No, wait!
什么? 埃尔莎 不 等下!
Give me my glove!
把手套给我!
Elsa, please. Please. I can't live like this anymore.
埃尔莎 求你了 我不能再这样过下去了
... Then leave.
那就离开
... What did I ever do to you?!
我到底做错了什么?
Enough, Anna.
别说了 安娜
No. Why? Why do you shut me out?!
不 为什么?为什么要把我关在门外?
Why do you shut the world out?!
为什么你把世界关在门外!
What are you so afraid of?!
你在怕什么?
I said, enough!
够了!
Sorcery. I knew there was
巫术 我就知道有
something dubious going on here.
什么可疑的事情在这里
Elsa...?
埃尔莎...?
There she is.
女王来了
Your Majesty! Long live the Queen! Queen Elsa...
陛下!女王万岁!女王...
Come drink with us.
来跟我们一起喝酒
Queen Elsa.
埃尔莎女王
Your Majesty? Are you all right?
女王陛下?你没事吧?
There she is! Stop her!
她在那!抓住她!
Please, just stay away from me.
离我远一点
Stay away!
走开!
Monster... Monster!
怪物...怪物!
Elsa!
埃尔莎!
Elsa...
埃尔莎...
Wait, Please!
等下!
Elsa, Stop!
埃尔莎 停下来!
Anna! No.
安娜!不
The Fjord.
海湾
Snow?
雪?
Yes, snow!
是雪!
Are you all right? No.
你没事吧? -有事
Did you know? No.
你知道这件事吗? -不知道
Look! It's snowing! It's snowing!
看! 下雪了!下雪了!
The Queen has cursed this land!
女王诅咒了这片土地!
She must be stopped!
一定要阻止她!
You have to go after her...Wait, no!
你得追上她 -等下 不!
You! Is there sorcery in you, too?
你也被下了巫术吗?
Are you a monster, too?
你也是怪物吗?
No. No. I'm completely ordinary.
不 我很普通
That's right she is.
没错她是很普通
... In the best way.
以最好的方式
And my sister's not a monster.
我姐姐也不是怪物
She nearly killed me.
她差点杀了我
You slipped on ice...Her ice!
你在..她的雪上滑到了!
It was an accident. She was scared.
是一次意外 她被吓坏了
She didn't mean it. She didn't mean any of this...
她不是有意的 她不是有意造成这一切的..
Tonight was my fault. I pushed her.
今晚错在我 是我刺激了她
So I'm the one that needs to go after her.
所以让我去追上她吧
What? Yeah. Bring me my horse, please.
什么? 把我的马牵来
Anna, no. It's too dangerous.
安娜 别这样 太危险了
Elsa's not dangerous.
埃尔莎一点也不危险
I'll bring her back, And I'll make this right.
我会带她回来 搞定这一切
I'm coming with you...No.
我跟你一起去.. 不
I need you here to take care of Arendelle.
我需要你帮我照顾安瑞戴尔
On my honor.
是我的荣幸
I leave Prince Hans in charge!
让汉斯王子来管事!
Are you sure you can trust her?
你确定能相信她吗?
I don't want you getting hurt.
我不想让你受伤
She's my sister,
她是我的姐姐
She would never hurt me.
她永远不会伤害我
The Snow glows white on the mountain tonight,
今夜的山林已被大雪覆盖
Not a footprint to be seen.
无人进入
A kingdom of isolation.
这样与世隔绝的王国
And it looks like I'm the Queen.
我才像是个女王
The wind is howling like this swirling storm inside.
大风呼啸 孕育着风暴
Couldn't keep it in, Heaven knows I tried...
再也藏不住 天知道我曾多么努力
Don't let them in, Don't let them see,
别让别人知道 别让别人看到
Be the good girl you always have to be.
你是个好姑娘 你必须一直是
Conceal, Don't feel, Don't let them know.
要隐藏 不要感受 不要让别人知道
Well, Now they know.
但是 现在 他们知道了
Let it go. Let it go.
随心而行 随心而行
Can't hold it back anymore.
反正再也无法隐瞒
Let it go. Let it go.
随心而行 随心而行
Turn away and Slam the door.
转过身 关上门
I don't care what they're going to say.
不在乎闲人闲语
Let the storm rage on.
让风暴怒吼吧
The cold never bothered me anyway.
严寒无法再侵扰我
It's funny how some distance makes everything seem small.
可笑的是 距离使一切变得渺小
And the fears that once controlled me.
曾经控制我的恐惧
Can't get to me at all.
再也无法使我困扰
It's time to see what I can do,
是时候展现真正的我了
To test the limits and Break through.
突破我的极限
No right, No wrong, No rules for me...
不再被规则所束缚
I'm free!
我自由了!
Let it go! Let it go!
随心而行 随心而行
I am one with the wind and sky.
驾驭着狂风与天空的我
Let it go! Let it go!
随心而行 随心而行
You'll never see me cry.
你不会看见我哭泣
Here I Stand And...
这就是我的立场
Here I'll stay.
这就是我的坚持
Let the storm rage on...
让风暴怒吼吧
My power flurries through the air into the ground.
我的魔力将从天而降
My soul is spiraling in frozen fractals all around.
我的灵魂随着四周的冰片盘旋而上
And one thought crystallizes like An icy blast...
思想化为结晶如一阵冰风
I'm never going back,
我不会再回头
The Past is in the Past!
过去已成为往事
Let it go! Let it go!
随心而行 随心而行
And I'll rise like the break of Dawn.
我将像旭日搬升起
Let it go! Let it go!
随心而行 随心而行
That perfect girl is gone.
那个完美女孩已不在了
Here I stand in the light of day.
我站在日光之下
Let the storm rage on!
让风暴怒吼吧!
The cold never bothered me anyway.
严寒无法再侵扰我
Elsa! Elsa!
埃尔莎! 埃尔莎!
Elsa, It's me, Anna...
埃尔莎 是我 安娜..
Your sister who didn't mean to make you freeze the summer.
你的妹妹不是要让你冰住夏天
I'm sorry. It's all my f-f-fault.
对不起 都是我的错
Of course, none of this would have happened
当然了 如果她把秘密告诉我的话
if she'd just told me her secret... ha...
这一切都不会发生
She's a stinker.
她真讨厌
Oh no. No. No. No. Come back. No.
不 回来 不
Oooo-Kay.
好吧
Snow, it had to be snow,
雪 到处都是雪
She couldn't have had tr-tr-tropical magic
她怎么会有把整个海湾
that covered the f-f-fjords in white sand and warm...
覆盖上白沙的热带魔法
Fire! Whoa!
火! 啊哈!
Wandering Oaken's Trading Post.
流浪橡树交易站
Ooh! And Sauna...
还有桑拿...
Big summer blow out.
夏季大甩卖
Half off swimming suits, clogs,
半价的泳装 目木底鞋
And a sun balm of my own invention, yah?
还有我自己发明的防晒霜?
Oh, great.
太好了
For now, how about boots,
鞋子怎么样
Winter boots... and dresses?
冬靴和..裙子?
That would be in our winter department.
那会是我们的冬季公寓
Oh. Um, I was just wondering; Has another young woman,
我有个问题 有没有一位年轻的女士
The Queen perhaps, I don't know, passed through here?
像是女王这样的人路过这里吗?
Only one crazy enough to be out in this storm is you, dear.
只有你这种疯子才会在这种风暴里乱走 亲爱的
You and this fellow... Hoo hoo.
你和这家伙
Big summer blow out.
夏季大甩卖
Carrots. Hah?
胡萝卜?
Behind you.
在你后面
Oh, right. Excuse me.
好吧 不好意思
A real howler in July, Yes?
一个真实的七月冰雪呼啸，不是吗?
Where ever could it be coming from?
究竟从哪里来的?
The North Mountain.
北部山脉
North Mountain.
That'll be forty.
一共要四十
Forty? No, ten.
四十?不 十
Oh dear, that's no good. See.
亲爱的 这可不好 看
These are from our winter stock,
这些是我们的冬季库存
where supply and demand have a big problem.
食物补给严重不足了
You want to talk about a supply and demand problem?
你想知道食物补给的问题?
I sell ice for a living.
我靠卖雪为生
Ooh, that's a rough business to be in right now.
这可是眼下难做的生意啊
I mean, that is really...
我是说 这可是真的...
Ahem. That's unfortunate.
真不幸
Still forty. But I will throw in a
不减价 但我会考虑去
visit to Oaken's sauna. Hoo hoo!
橡木桑拿看看
Hi, family.
嘿 一家子
Ten's all I got. Help me out.
我只有十块 帮帮我
Ten will get you this and no more.
十块只能用这个
Okay, just tell me one thing...What was
只要你告诉我一件事...
...happening on the North Mountain?
北部山脉上发生了什么?
Did it seem magical?
看起来像是魔法吗?
Yes! Now, back up
是的!退后
while I deal with this crook here.
看我怎么解决这个骗子
What did you call me?
你叫我什么?
Okay. Okay, I'm-Ow! Whoa!
好了 我是..
Bye bye.
拜拜
No Sven, I didn't get your carrots.
我没有帮你拿到胡萝卜 斯文
But I did find us a place to sleep.
但是找到了一个可以过夜的地方
And it's free.
免费哦
I'm sorry about this violence.
对暴力致以歉意
I will add a quart of lutefisk,
我请你吃自制的鳕鱼
So We'll have good feelings.
这样你就不会有坏感觉了
Just the outfit and boots, yah?
只要衣服和鞋子 对吗?
Reindeers are better than people.
驯鹿的心比人好
Sven, Don't you think that's true?
斯文 你觉得呢?
Yeah, People will beat you & Curse you & Cheat you.
是的 人类只会鞭打 诅咒 欺骗
Every one of em's bad, Except you.
所有人都是坏蛋 除了你哦
Oh, Thanks, Buddy.
谢了老兄
But People smell better than Reindeers.
但是人类比驯鹿要好闻一些
Sven, Don't you think I'm right?
斯文 你不赞同我吗?
That's once again true, For all Except you.
没错 除了你我都赞同
You got me. Let's call it a night.
好吧 说晚安吧
Good night.
晚安
Don't let the Frostbite bite.
别患上冻疮了
Nice duet.
漂亮的二重奏
Oh, it's just you.
只有你在说话而已
What do you want?
你想要什么?
I want you to take me up the North Mountain.
我想让你带我去北部山脉
I don't take people places.
我不喜欢人类居住的地方
Let me rephrase that...
让我换种表达方式...
Take me up the North Mountain...
请.. 带我去
Please.
北部山脉
Look, I know how to stop this winter.
听着 我懂得如何停止冬天
We leave at Dawn...
我们天一亮就出发...
And you forgot the carrots for Sven.
你忘了斯文的胡萝卜
Oops. Sorry. Sorry. I'm sorry. I didn't...
噢 对不起 对不起 对不起 我没有...
We leave now. Right now.
我们现在就走 马上走
Hang on! We like to go fast!
抓牢了!我想开快点!
I like fast!
我喜欢速度感!
Whoa, whoa! Get your feet down. This is fresh lacquer.
把你的脚放下 这才刚漆好
Seriously, were you raised in a barn?
说真的 你是在谷仓里被养大的?
Ew. No, I was raised in a castle.
不是 我是在城堡里长大的
So tell me, what made the Queen go all ice-crazy?
说一下 女王怎么会把冰弄的到处都是的
Oh well, it was all my fault.
这 是我的错
I got engaged but then she freaked out because...
因为我跟一个人订婚了所以她发狂了 因为...
I'd only just met him, you know, that day.
我才刚遇见那个人 在门打开的那一天
And she said she wouldn't bless the marriage...
她说她不会祝福我们的婚姻
Wait. You got engaged to someone you just met?
等下 你跟一个第一次碰到的人订婚了?
Yeah. Anyway, I got mad and so she got mad.
总之 我跟她都发疯了
And then she tried to walk away,
然后她准备离我们而去
and I grabbed her glove...
我抓脱了她的手套...
Hang on. You mean to tell me.
等下 你的意思是
You got engaged to someone you just met?!
你跟一个刚见面的人订婚了?
Yes. Pay attention. But the thing is...
别分心 关键是..
she wore the gloves all the time,
她从来不脱下她的手套
So I just thought, maybe she has a thing about dirt.
所以我觉得她可能隐瞒了什么
Didn't your parents ever warn you about strangers?
你父母没要你注意提防陌生人吗?
Yes, they did...
他们说过...
But Hans is not a stranger.
但汉斯不是陌生人
Oh yeah? What's his last name?
是吗?那他姓什么?
...Of-the-Southern-Isles?
姓..南部小岛?
What's his favorite food? Sandwiches.
他喜欢吃什么? -三明治
Best friend's name? Probably John.
最好的朋友呢? -大概是约翰
Eye color...Dreamy.
瞳孔的颜色..梦幻般的
Foot size? Foot size doesn't matter.
穿几码的鞋? -那不重要
Have you had a meal with him yet?
跟他吃过饭了吗?
What if you hate the way he eats?
如果你讨厌他的吃相怎么办?
What if you hate the way he picks his nose?
如果你讨厌他挖鼻孔的样子怎么办?
Picks his nose?
挖鼻孔?
And eats it.
和吃相
Excuse me, Sir. He's a Prince.
不好意思 他可是王子
All men do it.
男人都这样?
Ew. Look it doesn't matter, it's true love.
但这些都无关紧要 我们是真心爱着对方
Doesn't sound like true love.
听起来不像是真爱
Are you some sort of love expert?
你是什么情感专家吗?
No. But I have friends who are.
不是 但我有朋友是
You have friends who are love experts?
你是情感专家的朋友?
I'm not buying it...Stop talking.
我才不信..别胡说
No, no, no. I'd like to meet these...
不不 我想去见见这些...
No, I mean it.
我认真的
SHHH.
嘘
Sven, go. Go!
斯文 走!
What are they? Wolves.
它们是什么?狼
Wolves?
狼?
What do we do? I've got this.
我们怎么办?我有这个
You just... don't fall off and don't get eaten.
你..别掉下去给吃了就行
But I wanna help...No.
我想帮忙...不
Why not?
为什么不?
Because I don't trust your judgment.
因为我不相信你的判断
Excuse me?!
不好意思?
Who marries a man she just met?
谁跟陌生人结婚了?
It's true love!
我们真心相爱!
Christopher!
科里斯托彻!
It's Kristoff!
是克里斯托弗 !
Duck!
闪开!
- You almost set me on fire! - But I didn't.
你差点烧了我! -但我没有
Get ready to jump, Sven!
斯文 准备跳!
You don't tell him what to do!
你别告诉他怎么做!
I do! Jump, Sven!
我来! 跳 斯文!
But I just paid it off.
我才刚买的呢
Uh-oh. No, no, no.
不
Grab on!
抓牢!
Pull, Sven! Pull!
拉 斯文!拉!
I'll replace your sled and everything in it.
我会给你一个新的雪橇和里面所有的东西
And I understand if you don't want to help me anymore.
如果你不想帮我了我也理解
Of course I don't want to help her anymore.
我当然不想再帮她了
In fact, this whole thing has ruined me.
事实上 这事摧毁了我
For helping anyone ever again.
因为又帮助了人
- But she'll die on her own. - I can live with that.
但她自己去的话会死的 -我可以接受这点
But you won't get your new sled if she's dead.
如果她死了你就得不到新的雪橇了
You know sometimes I really don't like you.
有时我真的很讨厌你
Hold up. We're coming.
准备好 我们来了
You are?!
你们来了?
I mean, sure. I'll let you tag along.
当然了 跟着我吧
Arendelle...It's completely frozen.
安瑞戴尔已经被完全冰冻了
But it'll be fine. Elsa will thaw it.
但没事的 埃尔莎会解冻这里的
Will she? Yeah.
她会吗? -会的
Now come on. This way to the North Mountain?
来吧 这是去北部山脉的路吗?
More like this way.
这条路比较像
I never knew winter could be so beautiful.
从没想过冬天能这么美
YEAH... It really is beautiful, isn't it?
是的..真的很漂亮 不是吗?
But it's so white.
但有点太白了
You know, how about a little color?
你觉得 来点颜色如何?
I'm thinking like maybe some crimson, chartreuse...
来点绯红，淡黄绿色...
How 'bout yellow...no, not yellow.
黄色怎么样..不 黄色不行
Yellow and snow? Brrrr... no go.
黄色跟雪的配搭? 不行
Am I right?
我对吗?
Hi! You're creepy.
嗨!你太吓人了
I don't want it! Backatchya!
我不喜欢!拿回去!
- Please don't drop me. - Come on, it's just a head.
请别丢下我 -只是一个头而已
Don't!
别!
All right, we got off to a bad start.
好吧 我们的开头不是很好
Ew, ew, the body!
呃，身体!
Wait, what am I looking at right now?
等等，我看起来正常吗?
Why are you hanging off the earth like a bat?
为什么你们吊在地球上像蝙蝠一样
...Al'right. Wait one second.
好吧 等一下
Oooh! Thank you! You're welcome.
谢谢! -不用谢
Now I'm perfect.
现在我很完美了
Well, almost.
好吧 差不多了
It was like my whole life got upside down.
好像我的一生都在颠倒中度过
Oh! Too hard. I'm sorry! I was just...
哦 太重了  对不起 -我只是...
Woo! Head Rush! Are you okay?
喔!头部冲击!   你没事吧?
Are you kidding me? I am wonderful!
你在说笑吗?我感觉好极了!
I've always wanted a nose.
我一直想要个鼻子
So cute. It's like a little baby unicorn.
真可爱 像个独角兽宝宝
What? Hey! Whoa.
什么? -嘿!
Oh, I love it even more! Hah...
我更喜欢这样!哈..
All right, let's start this thing over.
好了 让我们结束这件事吧
Hi everyone. I'm Olaf. And I like warm hugs.
大家好 我是雪宝 喜欢温暖的拥抱
Olaf?
雪宝?
That's right, Olaf.
没错 我就是雪宝
And you are?
你呢?
Oh, um... I'm Anna.
我是 安娜
And who's the funky-looking donkey over there?
那边那只滑稽的驴是谁?
That's Sven.
是斯文
Uh-huh. And who's the reindeer?
那驯鹿又是谁?
Sven.
斯文.
They're...oh, okay...Makes things easier for me.
他们是... 好吧 这样好理解多了
Ha. Aw, look at him tryin' to kiss my nose.
哈 他想亲我的鼻子
I like you, too!
我也喜欢你!
Olaf, Did Elsa build you?
雪宝 你是埃尔莎堆出来的吗?
Yeah. Why?
是的 怎么了?
You know where she is? Yeah. Why?
你知道她在哪里吗? -是的 怎么了?
Do you think you could show us the way?
你能带我们去见她吗?
Yeah. Why? How does this work?
是的 怎么了?这个怎么用?
Stop it, Sven. Trying to focus here.
停下来斯文 专心点
Yeah, Why? I'll tell you Why.
好的 怎么了? -我会告诉你怎么了
We need Elsa to Bring back Summer.
我们要找到埃尔莎把夏天带回来
Summer? Uhum.
夏天? 对啊
Oh, I don't know why but.
不知道为什么但是
I've always loved the idea of summer,
我一直很喜欢夏天这主意
And Sun, and all things hot.
还有阳光，所有的东西都很热
Really?
真的?
I'm guessing you don't have much experience with heat.
我想你大概对热没什么经验
Nope!
是没有!
But sometimes I like to close my eyes
但我有时会闭上双眼
and imagine what it'd be like when summer does come.
想像夏天来到时会是什么样子
Bees'll Buzz, Kids'll blow dandelion fuzz.
蜜蜂嗡嗡叫，蒲公英漫天飞
And I'll be doing whatever snow does in summer.
我会做所有雪人在夏天该做的事情
A drink in my hand, My snow up against the burning sand.
我拿着一杯饮料，雪白的身体躺在燃烧的沙滩上
Prob'ly getting gorgeously tanned in Summer.
应该能在夏天晒个漂亮的古铜色
I'll finally see a summer breeze,
我将终能看见夏天的气息
blow away a winter storm.
吹走冬天的暴风雪
And find out what happens to
然后发现
solid water, When it gets warm.
冰冻的水变得温暖
And I can't wait to see, what my buddies all think of me.
我等不及要看看我同伴对我的想法
Just imagine how much cooler I'll be in summer!
想像一下我在夏天会有多酷吧
The hot and the cold are both so intense,
炎热和寒冷都是如此的剧烈
Put 'em together, It just makes sense!
把它们放在一起，刚刚好啊
Winter's a good time to stay in and cuddle,
冬天是个待在室内相互依偎的好时节
But put me in summer and I'll be a...
但在夏天我会变成
Happy Snowman!
快乐的雪人!
When life gets rough I like to hold on to my dream
生活困苦时 我要坚持梦想
of relaxing in the summer sun just letting off steam!
梦中享受那令人放松的夏天艳阳
Oh the sky will be Blue...
天空多么湛蓝
And you guys'll be there too.
你们也将会在那里
When I finally do what frozen things do in Summer!
当我终于在夏天做这些冰制物应该做的事时
- I'm gonna tell him. - Don't you dare.
我要告诉它 -你敢?
In Summer!
在夏天!
So, Come on! Elsa's this way.
快点! 埃尔莎在这边
Let's go bring back summer!
让我们去带回夏天!
I'm coming!
我来了!
Somebody's got to tell him.
总得有人告诉它
No. No. You've got the bark facing down.
不 你得把树皮朝下
The bark needs to be face-up.
树皮需要朝上
Bark down is drier.
朝下太干燥了
Bark up...Bark down.
朝上 朝下
Cloak. Does anyone need a cloak?
有人需要斗篷吗?
Arendelle is indebted to you, Your Highness.
安瑞戴尔非常感激你 陛下
The castle is open. There's soup
城堡大门开了 里面有热汤
and hot glogg in the Great Hall.
大厅里还有热饮
Here. Pass these out.
来 把这些传下去
Prince Hans, are we just
汉斯王子 难道我们
expected to sit here and freeze
就坐在这眼睁睁看着
while you give away all of Arendelle's Tradable goods?
你把安瑞戴尔的贸易物资通通都送出去?
Princess Anna has given her orders and...
安娜公主下了命令...
And that's another thing,
这是另一回事
has it dawned on you that your Princess
你渐渐明白了你的公主
may be conspiring with a wicked sorceress...
可能跟一个邪恶的女巫串通好了
to destroy us all?
准备杀光我们吗?
Do not question the Princess. She left me in charge,
不准质疑公主 她让我掌管这里
and I will not hesitate to
我会毫不犹豫的
protect Arendelle from treason.
严惩对安瑞戴尔犯了叛国罪的人
Treason?!
叛国罪?
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa, boy. Easy. Easy.
哇!放轻松点 孩子
Princess Anna's horse. What happened to her? Where is she?
安娜公主的马 她怎么了?她在哪?
Princess Anna is in trouble.
安娜公主陷入麻烦了
I need volunteers to go with me to find her!
我需要志愿者跟我一起去找回她!
I volunteer two men, my Lord!
我派遣两个志愿者 陛下!
Be prepared for anything,
做好准备
And should you encounter the Queen,
你们遇到女王时
You are to put an end to this winter.
就得结束这个冬天
Do you understand?
明白吗?
So how exactly are you planning to stop this weather?
你有什么具体的计划来结束这个冬天吗?
Oh, I am gonna talk to my sister.
我要跟我姐姐谈一谈
That's your plan? My ice business is
这就是你的计划? 我的冰雪生意就赌在
riding on you talking to your sister.
你跟你的姐姐谈一谈上?
Yup.
是的
So you're not at all afraid of her?
你不怕她吗?
Why would I be? Yeah.
我为什么要怕她?
I bet Elsa's the nicest, gentlest,
我敢说埃尔莎是世界上最好最温柔
Warmest person ever.
最热心的人了
Oh, look at that.
看看那个
I've been impaled.
简直绝望
What now?
现在怎么办?
It's too steep. I've only got one rope,
太陡了 我只有一根绳子
And you don't know how to climb mountains.
你连爬山都不会吗?
Says who?
谁说的?
What are you doing?
你在做什么?
I'm going to see my sister.
我要去见我的姐姐
You're going to kill yourself. I wouldn't put my foot there.
你会弄死自己的 我不会把脚放在这里的
You're distracting me...Or there.
你让我分心了 -或那里
How do you know Elsa even wants to see you?
你怎么知道埃尔莎想要见你?
I'm just blocking you out 'cause
我现在不能理你因为
I gotta concentrate here.
我要专心一点
You know, most people who disappear
大多数在山上消失的人都
into the mountains want to be alone.
是想单独行动的人
Nobody wants to be alone. Except maybe you...
没人喜欢一个人 大概除了你
I'm not alone...I have friends, remember?
我不孤独...我有朋友的 记得吗?
You mean the love experts?
你是说情感专家?
Yes, the love experts!
没错 情感专家!
Please tell me I'm almost there.
请告诉我快到了吧
Does the air seem a bit thin to you up here?
有觉得你那的空气有些稀薄吗?
Hang on...Hey, Sven?
坚持住..嘿 斯文?
Not sure if this is going to solve the problem, but I found
不确定这有没有用但我找到一个
a staircase that leads exactly where you want it to go.
通向你想去的地方的梯子
Ha ha. Thank goodness. Catch!
哈哈 谢天谢地 抓住了!
Thanks! That was like a crazy trust exercise.
谢了!这像是一次疯狂的信任练习
Now that's ice. I might cry.
如果那是冰做的 我可能会哭
Go ahead. I won't judge.
继续吧 我不会评价你的
All right, take it easy. Come here, I gotcha.
好了 放松点 来这边 我抓住你了
Okay. You stay right here, buddy.
好了伙计 你待在这里
Flawless.
完美无瑕
Knock... Just knock...
敲门吧..
Why isn't she knocking...?
她为什么不敲门?
Do you think she knows how to knock?
你觉得她知道如何敲门吗?
It opened. That's a first.
门开了 这是第一次
You should probably wait out here.
你们应该在这里等
What?
什么?
Last time I introduced her to a guy, she froze everything.
上一次我向他介绍了一个男孩 她就把所有的东西都冰住了
But. But...Oh come on, It's a palace made of ice.
但是..好吧 是一座冰之宫殿
Ice is my life...Bye, Sven.
冰就是我的生命..再见 斯文
You too, Olaf.
你也是 雪宝
Me? Just give us a minute.
我? 给我点时间
Okay.
好的
One... two... Three... four...
一..二..三..四..
Elsa? It's me... Anna.
埃尔莎?是我..安娜
Anna?
安娜?
Wow... Elsa, you look different...
哇..埃尔莎 你看起来很不一样...
It's a good different...And this place.
是好的一方面...这地方..
Is amazing...Thank you.
很漂亮 -谢谢
I never knew what I was capable of.
我不知道我可以这样
I'm so sorry about what happened. If I'd known...
对于发生的事情我感到很抱歉 如果知道..
No, it's okay.
没事的
You don't have to apologize.
你不需要抱歉
But you should probably go, please.
但你需要离开这里
But I just got here.
但我才来呢
You belong in Arendelle.
你属于安瑞戴尔
So do you...No, Anna. I belong here.
你也是啊... -不 安娜 我属于这里
Alone.
独自一人
Where I can be who I am,
只有在这里
Without hurting anybody.
我才不会伤害到任何人
Actually, about that...58... 59... 60.
实际上 关于这点 58..59..60
Wait. What is that?
等下 那是什么?
Hi, I'm Olaf and I like warm hugs.
嗨 我是喜欢温暖拥抱的雪宝
Olaf?
雪宝?
You Built me. You remember that?
你堆了我 不记得了吗?
And You're alive?
你还活着?
Um... I think so?
恩..我想是吧?
He's just like the one we built as kids.
他和我们小时候堆的那个雪人一模一样
Yeah!
是!
So we were so close.
我们曾是如此的亲密
We can be like that again.
现在也行啊
Slow Down...
慢一点...
Anna!
安娜!
No, We can't.
不行了
Goodbye, Anna...Elsa, wait...
再见 安娜... -埃尔莎 等下...
No, I'm just trying to protect you.
你不懂 我只是想保护你
You don't have to protect me. I'm not afraid.
你不需要保护我 我不怕
Please don't shut me out again.
请别再把我关在外面了
Please don't slam the door.
别再关上那扇门
You don't have to keep your distance anymore.
你我之间不需要距离
'Cause for the first time in forever,
因为这一次
I finally understand.
我终于明白
For the first time in forever, We can fix this hand in hand.
因为这一次 我们能携手度过难关
We can head down this mountain Together.
我们能携手离开这里
You don't have to live in fear.
不再生活在恐惧之下
'Cause for the first time in forever,
因为这一次
I will be right here.
我在你身边
Anna, Please go back home.
安娜 回去吧
Your life awaits.
你的人生在等着你
Go enjoy the sun And open up the gates.
回去享受阳光并打开那些门
Yeah, But...I know! You mean well,
但是.. -我知道!你的想法很好
But leave me be.
但是把我留在这
Yes, I'm alone. But I'm alone and Free.
虽然我很孤单 但是我很自由
Just stay away and you'll be safe from me.
离我远点就不会伤害到你
- Actually, We're not. - What do you mean You're not?
实际上 并不是这样 -并不是这样是什么意思?
I get the feeling you don't know?
你没察觉到吗?
What do I not know?
没察觉到什么?
Arendelle's in deep deep deep deep snow.
安瑞戴尔被雪深深深深的覆盖了
What?
什么?
You kind of set off an eternal winter...everywhere.
你似乎在全世界下了一场大雪...
Everywhere?
全世界?
It's okay, you can just unfreeze it.
没关系 你可以融化它
No, I can't.
不 我做不到
I don't know how...Sure you can.
我不知道如何.. -你当然可以
I know you can!
我相信你可以!
'Cause for the first time in forever,
因为这是第一次
I'm such a Fool! I can't be Free!
我真笨!我不自由!
You don't have to be afraid.
你不需要感到害怕
No escape From the storm inside of me!
无法逃离我内心的风暴!
We can work this out together.
我们可以携手共渡难关
I can't control the curse!
我控制不了诅咒!
We'll reverse the storm you've made.
我们会改变你造成的这场风暴
Anna, Please, You'll only make it worse!
安娜 你只会事情变得更糟!
Don't panic.
别惊慌
There's so much fear!
太让人害怕了!
We'll make the sun shine bright.
我们会让太阳重见天日
You're not safe here!
你在这里不安全!
We can face this thing together...
我们携手面对...
I can't!
我做不到!
Anna. Are you okay?
安娜 你还好吗?
I'm okay... I'm fine...Who's this?
我还好... 这是谁?
Wait, it doesn't matter. Just...You have to go.
等下 这不重要 你必须得走了
No, I know we can figure this out together...
不 我肯定我们能一起解决这事的..
How? What power do you have to stop this winter?
怎么做?什么力量可以让你结束这个冬天?
To stop me?
阻止我?
Anna, I think we should go.
安娜 我们得走了
No. I'm not leaving without you, Elsa.
不 我不能丢下你 埃尔莎
Yes, you are.
是，你要
Stop. Put us down!
停下来 把我们放下来!
Go away!
离开这里!
Heads up!
小心!
Watch out for my butt!
小心我的屁股!
It is not nice to throw people!
丢人是不好的!
Wow, Wow, Wow Feisty pants. Ok, Relax.
哇 小调皮 冷静下来
Just Calm down. Calm down.
冷静 冷静
All Right. I'm Okay.
好了 我好了
Just let the snow man be.
让雪人做它该做的
I'm Calm...Great.
我得冷静下来..很好
Oh... Come on!
不要吧!
Uh-oh. See. Now you made him mad!
看到没 你让他生气了!
I'll distract him.
我会引开他
You guys go.
你们先走
No, no, not you guys.
不 不 不是你们
This just got a whole lot harder.
这只是让事情变的更困难了
What are you doing?
你在做什么?
I got him!
我打到他了!
It's a hundred foot drop.
这有一百多英尺深
It's two hundred.
是两百
- What's that for? - I'm digging a snow anchor.
那是干什么? -我在挖一个雪锚
Okay. What if we fall?
好的，如果我们掉下去怎么办?
There's twenty feet of fresh powder down there.
下面有二十多尺深的新雪
It'll be like landing on a pillow...
会像掉在枕头上一样...
Hopefully.
希望如此
Okay, Anna. On three.
好了 安娜 数三下
One...Okay. You tell me when...
一...好了 你告诉我什么时候...
Two...I'm ready to go...I was born ready! Yes!
二..我准备好..我一生下来就准备好了!耶!
Calm down.
冷静下来
Tree!
三!
What the... Whoa! That happened.
这什么..哇! 发生了
Ah. Ah. Man, am I out of shape.
哦，天哪，我都变形了
There we go. Hey, Anna! Sven!
就这样 嘿 安娜! 斯文!
Where'd your guys go? We totally lost Marshmallow back there!
你们去哪了? -我们完全找不着棉花糖了!
Hey. We were just talking about you.
嘿 我们刚刚在谈论你
Ll good things, all good things.
都是说的好话 都是好话
No!
不!
This is not making much of a difference! Is it?
好像没什么作用
Olaf!
雪宝!
Hang in there, guys! Go Faster!
坚持住伙计们!快点!
Wait, what?
等下 什么?
Kristoff!
克里斯托弗!
Don't come back!
别回来!
We won't.
我们不会
Hey, you were right. Just like a pillow.
嘿 你没说错 就跟摔在枕头上一样
Olaf!
雪宝!
I can't feel my legs!
我的腿没有知觉了!
Those are my legs.
是我的腿
Ooh. Hey, do me a favor, grab my butt.
嘿 帮我个忙 抓下我的屁股
Oh, That feels better.
哦 感觉好多了
Hey, Sven! He found us.
嘿 斯文! -他找到我们了
Who's my cute little reindeer?
谁是我的可爱小驯鹿?
Don't talk to him like that.
别这样跟他说话
Here.
这里
You okay? Thank you.
没事吧? -谢谢
Um... How's your head?
你的头怎么了?
I mean, It's fine. Ah... I'm good.
没事的 我很好
Ha. I've got a thick skull.
哈 我有点头脑迟钝
I don't have a skull...Or bones.
我没有头骨..或者说我没有骨头
So...
所以..
So Now what? Now what?
现在怎么办?怎么办?
Now what?!
现在?
Oooh! What am I gonna do?
噢!我准备怎么做?
She threw me out. I can't go back to.
她把我扔出来了 我不能回
Arendelle with the weather like this.
安瑞戴尔 跟这里的天气一样
And then there's your ice business...
而且还有你的冰雪生意也...
Hey, hey, don't worry about my ice business...
嘿 嘿 别担心我的冰雪生意
Worry about your hair? What?
那担心你的头发吗? -什么?
Just fell off a Cliff. You should see your hair.
刚从悬崖上摔下来 -你应该看看你的头发
- No, yours is turning white. - White? It's... what?
你的头发变白了 -白了? 什么?
It's because she struck you, isn't it?
因为她攻击了你 对吗?
Does it look bad?
看起来糟糕吗?
No. You hesitated.
不 -你犹豫了
No, I didn't. Anna, you need help. Okay? Come on.
我没有 安娜 你需要帮助 好吗? 来吧
Okay! Where are we going? To see my friends.
好的! 我们去哪? -去找我的朋友们
The love experts? Love experts?!
那个情感专家? 情感专家?
And don't worry, they'll be able to fix this.
别担心 他们会解决一切的
How do you know?
你怎么知道?
Because I've seen them do it before.
因为我见他们曾做过一次这种事
I like to consider myself a love expert.
我觉得我自己就是感情专家
Get it together. Control it.
集中它 控制它
Don't feel. Don't feel.
别感受 别感受
Don't feel!
别感受!
Look, Sven. The sky's awake.
看 斯文 天要亮了
Are you cold? A little.
你冷吗? -有点
Wait. Come here.
等下 过来
So, About my friends...
那么 关于我的朋友们...
Well, I say friends, they're more like family...
虽说是朋友 对于我来说更像是家人...
Anyway, when I was a kid, it was just me and Sven
总之 我小的时候只有斯文陪着我
until you know, they took us in.
直到他们发现了我
They did? Yeah.
他们发现了你? -是的
I don't want to scare you, they can be
并不是想吓唬你 他们有些
a little bit inappropriate...
做的不合适的地方..
And loud... very loud...
有些吵..非常的吵...
They're also stubborn at times, And a little.
有时有些倔强 还有点
Overbearing. And heavy. Really, really heavy. Which you...
傲慢 而且很重 非常非常的重
But You know, you okay. They're fine. They mean well.
但你得知道你会没事的 他们很不错  都是好人
Kristoff, they sound wonderful.
克里斯托弗 他们听起来很不错
Okay then...
好吧
Meet my family.
见一见我的家人吧
Hey, guys!
嘿 伙计们!
They're rocks.
都是石头
He's crazy.
他疯了
Hey, Wow...I pretty recognize you, What's so much weigh?
嘿...我似乎认识你 为何会这么重?
I'll distract them while you run.
我一引开他们你就跑
Hi, Sven's family! It's nice to meet you!
嗨 斯文的家人! 很高兴见到你们!
Anna, because I love you, I insist you run.
安娜 因为我爱你 所以 需要你跑
Understand you're love experts!
我知道你就是情感专家!
Why aren't you running?
你为什么不逃走?
Okay. Um... I'm gonna go...
好吧 我正准备...
No, no, no. Anna, wait!
不 安娜 等下!
Kristoff!
克里斯托弗!
Kristoff's home!
克里斯托弗的家!
Kristoff! Kristoff's home! It's been too long!
克里斯托弗!克里斯托弗的家!太久了!
Kristoff's home!
克里斯托弗的家!
Wait? Kristoff?
等下? 克里斯托弗?
Yeah...Oh, let me look at you!
是的 让我瞧瞧你!
Oh, take off your clothes, Kristoff, I wash them.
脱下你的外套 克里斯托弗 我会帮你弄干净的
Ah! No. I'm gonna keep my clothes on, Look.
不用了 我穿着就好 听着
Great to see you all.
见到你们很高兴
But where's grand Pabbie? He's napping.
但是大帕比在哪? -他在午睡
But look, I grew a mushroom.
看 我种了一个蘑菇
And I earned my fire Crystal.
我获得了一块火焰水晶
I passed a kidney Stone.
我治好了我的肾结石
Kristoff, Pick me up.
克里斯托弗 抱我
You're getting big...Good for you.
你在变大..是好事
Trolls? They're trolls.
巨魔?他们是巨魔
He's brought a girl!
他带回来一个女孩!
What's going on?
怎么了?
I've learned to just roll with it.
我已经学会怎么应付
Let me see. Bright eyes. Working nose. Strong teeth.
我看看你 明亮的大眼睛 小巧的鼻子 坚硬的牙齿
Yes, yes, yes. She'll do nicely for our Kristoff.
好的好的 她能帮上克里斯托弗很大的忙的
Wait. Oh. Um. No.
等下 哦不
You've got the wrong idea. That's not why I brought her here.
你错了 不是因为这个我才带她来的
Right. We're not. I'm not...
我们不是 我不是...
What's the issue, dear?
怎么了 亲爱的?
Why are you holding back from such a man?
你们为什么向他隐瞒这事
Is it the clumpy way he walks?
因为他笨拙的走路姿势?
What?
什么?
Or the Grumpy way he talks? No.
还是他爱抱怨的说话方式? -不是
Or the pear-shaped, square-shaped
还是说他像梨子一样方形
...weirdness of his feet? Hey!
奇怪的脚? -嘿!
And though we know he washes well
尽管我们都知道他很爱干净
he always ends up Sorta smelly.
他还是有股怪味
But You'll never meet a fella who's as sensitive and sweet.
但你永远也找不到另外一个比他还要体贴温柔的人了
That's nice. but...
很好  不过
So he's a bit of a fixer upper,
所以他需要一点改善
So he's got a few flaws,
他还有些小缺点
His peculiar brain, Dear. His thing for the reindeer.
有时候他的想法有点独特 亲爱的 比如他和他的驯鹿
- That outside a few of nature's laws. - This is not about me!
有点超出自然规律 这说的不是我!
So he's a bit of a fixer upper,
所以他需要一点改善
But this we're certain of...
可我们担保
You Can fix this fixer upper up with a little bit of love.
你只用一点点的爱就能改善他
Can we just stop talking about this?!
我们能不谈这个吗!
We've got a real, actual problem here.
我们来这里是因为遇到了真正的麻烦
I'll Say...So tell me dear, Is it the way that he runs scared?
我来说...亲爱的你告诉我 是不是因为他跑步的姿势让你害怕
Or that he's Socially Impaired?
或是因为他社交能力低下?
Or that he only likes to tinkle in the Woods?
还是因为他成天只知道在林子里晃悠?
I do not need to know that.
我不需要知道这些
Are you holding back your fondness.
你隐藏你的喜欢是因为
Due to his unmanly blondeness?
他的金发没有男人味?
Or the way he covers up that he's the honest goods?
还是他隐瞒自己是最适合的那个人的方式?
He's just a bit of a fixer upper.
他只是需要一点改善
He's got a couple a' bugs.
他还有一些小缺点
No, I don't.
我没有
His isolation is confirmation of
他的离群是因为
his desperation for healing hugs.
他从没尝过安慰的拥抱
So he's a bit of a fixer upper, But we know what to do.
所以他需要一点改善，而且我们知道该怎么做
The way to fix up this fixer
治好他的固执的方法
...upper is to fix him up with you.
是和你在一起 就能治好他
Stop it. Stop it. Stop it. Enough!
停停停，够了!
She's engaged to someone else. Okay?!
她已经和别人订婚了，好吗?
So she's a bit of a fixer upper,
那她也需要一点改善
That's a minor thing.
小事一桩
This quote “engagement” Is a flex arrangement.
“订婚”是可以改变的
And by the way, I don't see no Ring.
况且我也没见到订婚戒指
So she's a bit of a fixer upper,
所以她也需要一点改善
Her brain's a bit betwixt.
她的思想有点摇摆不定
Get the fiance out of the way And
把她的未婚夫踢出去就
the whole thing will be fixed!
万事俱备!
We aren't saying you can change him.
我们不是说你可以改变他
'Cause people don't really change.
因为人们不会真正的改变
We're only saying that love's a force.
我们只是说爱是一种力量
That's powerful and strange.
它力量无穷，神奇无比
People make bad choices if they're
人们会做出错误的选择，如果他们
mad or scared or stressed.
在疯狂、受惊吓或者紧张的情况下
But throw a little love their way...
但只要给他们一些爱
throw a little love their way.
给他们一些爱
And you'll bring out their best!
你就会让他们做到最好
True love brings out the best!
真爱让人做到最好!
Everyone's a bit of a fixer upper,
每个人都需要一点改善
That's what it's all about.
这就是意义所在
Father, Sister, Brother We need each other
父母姐妹兄弟 我们需要彼此
to raise us up and round us out.
来伴随我们成长
Everyone's a bit of a fixer upper,
每个人都需一点改善
But when push comes to shove.
但是在紧要关头
The only fixer upper fixer that can fix a fixer upper is.
能真正改善我们就是
True, True, True, True, Love.
真正的 真正的 真正的 真正的，爱
Love, Love, Love, True Love...True-e-e-e-e-e.
爱 爱 爱 真爱 真正的
Do you, Anna, take Kristoff to be your trollfully wedded...
安娜，你是否愿意嫁给克里斯托夫
Wait, what?!
等等，什么?
You're getting married.
你们要结婚啦
She's as cold as ice.
她冷的像冰
There's strange magic here!
有一股奇怪的魔法!
Grand Pabbie! Bring her to me.
大帕比!  把她给我
Anna, your life is in danger.
安娜 你陷入危险之中
There is ice in your heart, put there by your sister.
你的心里有一块冰 被你姐姐放进去的
If not removed, to solid ice will you freeze, forever.
如果不拿开的话这块冰会冻住你的心 直到永远
What ...? No.
什么?不会吧
But you can remove it, Right?
但你能帮我移开 对吗?
I can not, I'm sorry Kristoff...
我做不到 对不起 克里斯托弗...
If it was her head that would be easy.
如果是她的头的话就会容易很多
But only an act of true love can thaw a frozen heart.
但只有真爱之举才能融化冰封的心
An act of true love?
真爱之举?
A true love's kiss, perhaps?
一个真爱之吻 可能?
Anna, we've got to get you back to Hans.
安娜 我们得带你去找汉斯
Hans.
汉斯.
Pull us out, Sven.
带我们出发吧 斯文
Olaf! Come on. I'm coming!
雪宝! 来吧 -我来了!
Let's go kiss Hans! Who is this Hans?!
让我们去亲汉斯吧! -谁是汉斯?
We are here to find Princess Anna.
我们是来找安娜公主的
Be on guard,
保持警惕
but no harm is to come to the Queen.
女王不会伤害我们的
Do you understand? Yes, Sir.
明白吗? -是的
The Queen.
女王
Up there! Come on!
上来这边!快!
No, Please.
请别这样
Stay away!
站远点!
Fire! Fire.
火!小心火
Get her! Get her!
抓住她  抓住她!
Queen Elsa!
埃尔莎女王!
Don't be the monster they fear you are.
别变成他们害怕的怪物了
No... What have I done?
不..我都做了什么?
Why did you bring me here?
为什么把我带到这里来?
I couldn't just let them kill you.
我不能让他们杀了你
But I'm a danger to Arendelle. Get Anna.
但我对于安瑞戴尔是个威胁 找到安娜
Anna has not returned...
安娜还没回来...
If you would just stop the winter,
请你停下这场严冬
bring back summer... please.
把夏天还回来...求你了
Don't you see... I can't.
你还不明白..我做不到
You have to tell them to let me go.
你得命令他们让我走
I will do what I can.
我会做我所能做的
- Just hang in there. - Come on, buddy, faster!
撑住 -快点伙计!
I'll meet you guys at the castle!
在城堡里面见面!
Stay out of sight, Olaf!
别给发现了 雪宝!
I will!
知道啦!
It's Princess Anna!
是安娜公主!
Are you g-gonna be okay?
你会 会没事的吗?
Don't worry about me.
别担心我了
Anna! Oh, you had us worried sick...My Lady.
安娜!你让我们担心惨了...
Get her warm and find Prince Hans, immediately.
给她温暖  把汉斯王子找来 快
We will. Thank you.
遵命 -谢谢
Make sure she's safe!
保证她的安全!
I'm going back out to look for Princess Anna.
我要回去找安娜公主
You cannot risk going out there again.
你不能再冒险出去了
If anything happens to her...
如果她发生了任何不测..
If anything happens to the Princess,
如果公主身上发生了任何不测
you are all Arendelle has left.
你就是安瑞戴尔唯一的继承人了
He's in here. Prince Hans.
他来了 汉斯王子
Anna. You're so cold.
安娜 你怎么这么冷
Hans, you have to kiss me...What?
汉斯 吻我.. -什么?
Now. Now.
现在
We'll give you two some privacy.
我们会给你们一些私人空间
What happened out there?
到底发生什么了?
Elsa struck me with her powers.
埃尔莎用魔法攻击了我
You said she'd never hurt you.
你说她永远不会伤害你
I was wrong.
我错了
Anna?
安娜?
She froze my heart and only an act of true love can save me.
她冰住了我的心 只有真爱之举才可以救我
A true love's kiss.
一个真爱之吻
Oh, Anna...
安娜...
If only there was someone out there who loved you.
这里要真有人爱你就好了
What?
什么?
You said you did.
你说过你是的
As thirteenth in line in my own
作为我们王国的第十三个王子
...kingdom, I didn't stand a chance. I knew...
我一点机会都没有 我知道的..
I'd have to marry into the throne somewhere...
我一定要娶一个女王什么的..
What are you talking about?
你在说什么?
As heir, Elsa was preferable, of course.
当然了 埃尔莎是一个完美的继承者
But no one was getting anywhere with her.
跟她在一起是不会有进展的
But you...Hans?
但是你呢 汉斯?
You were so desperate for love,
你是如此渴望爱情
You were willing to marry me, just like that.
你愿意嫁给我 不是吗
I figured, after we married, I'd have
我想了想 在我们结婚后 我会为埃尔莎
to stage a little accident for Elsa.
制造一点小意外
Hans. No, stop.
汉斯 不 别说了
But then she doomed herself, and you were
可她已经毁了自己 而你
...dumb enough to go after her.
傻到去救她
Please.
求你了
All that's left now is to kill Elsa and bring back summer.
现在唯一的办法就是杀了埃尔莎并把夏天带回来
You're no match for Elsa.
你不是埃尔莎的对手
No, you're no match for Elsa.
不 你才不是埃尔莎的对手
I, on the other hand, am the hero who is
而我 则是将安瑞戴尔从毁灭中
going to save Arendelle from destruction.
拯救出来的英雄
You won't get away with this.
你是逃不了的
Oh, I already have.
我已经做到了
Please, somebody help.
救命
Please, please!
救命!
It's getting colder by the minute.
我越来越冷了
If we don't do something soon, We'll all freeze to death.
如果不做点什么的话就会被冻死的
Prince Hans...Princess Anna is...
汉斯王子 安娜公主已经..
Dead. What...?
死了 -什么?
What happened to her?
她怎么了?
She was killed by Queen Elsa.
她被埃尔莎女王杀死了
Her own sister.
她的亲姐姐
At least we got to say our marriage vows...
至少我们念了婚誓
before she died in my arms.
在她死在我怀抱中之前
There can be no doubt now,
现在毋庸置疑
Queen Elsa is a monster and we are all in grave danger.
埃尔莎女王是一个陷我们于险境的怪物
Prince Hans, Arendelle looks to you.
汉斯王子 安瑞戴尔听你的
With a heavy heart,
带着沉重的心
I charge Queen Elsa of Arendelle with treason
我宣布埃尔莎女王以叛国罪将被
and sentence her to death.
处以死刑
Hurry Up!
快!
She's dangerous. Move quickly and be careful.
她是个危险人物 动作快些 要小心
The Door not open!
门打不开!
What is it, buddy? Hey, watch it.
这是什么老兄? -嘿 看着
What's wrong with you?
你到底怎么了?
I don't understand you when you talk like that.
你这样说话我可听不懂
Ah! Stop it! Put me down!
啊 停下来!把我放下来!
No, Sven! We're not going back!
不 斯文! 我们不会回去!
She's with her true love.
她跟她的真爱在一起了
What the...
什么...
Anna!
安娜!
Help.
救命
Anna. Oh no.
安娜! 不
Olaf? Olaf. Get away from there.
雪宝? 雪宝 逃离这里
So this is heat... I love it.
这就是热吗.. 我喜欢
Ooh! But don't touch it!
别碰它!
So, where's Hans? What happened to your kiss?
汉斯在哪? 你的吻怎么样了?
I was wrong about him. It wasn't true love.
我看错他了 那不是真爱
Huh. But we ran all the way here?
那我们不是白跑了?
Please Olaf, you can't stay here, you'll melt.
雪宝听我说 你不能待在这里 你会被融化的
I am not leaving here until we find
在找到能拯救你的真爱之前
...some other act of true love to save you.
我是不会离你而去的
Do you happen to have any ideas?
你有主意了吗?
I don't even know what love is.
爱是什么我都不知道
That's okay, I do...Love is...
我知道 爱是..
putting someone else's needs before yours, like, you know,
在你需要帮忙的时候帮助你 你知道的
how Kristoff brought you back here
为了救你克里斯托弗把你带给汉斯然后
to Hans and left you forever.
又离开了你
Kristoff loves me?
克里斯托弗喜欢我?
Wow, you really don't know anything about love, do you?
你真的不知道爱是什么东西 对吗?
Olaf, you're melting.
雪宝 你在融化
Some people are worth melting for.
有些人是值得为之融化的
Just maybe not right this second.
可能现在不是时候
Don't worry, I've got it!
别担心 我来处理
We're going to get through...
我们会撑过去...
Oh, wait. Hang on. I'm getting something.
等下 坚持住 我看到些东西
It's Kristoff and Sven! They're coming back this way.
是克里斯托弗和斯文 他们回来了
They-they are?
他们回来了?
Wow, he's really moving fast. Huh...I guess I was wrong.
他跑的很快..呃 我想我错了
I guess Kristoff doesn't love
我猜克里斯托弗不够爱你
...you enough to leave you behind.
所以离开你
Help me up, Olaf. Please.
帮我起来 雪宝
No, no, no, no, no. You need to
不不 你需要
stay by the fire and keep warm.
靠近火来保持温暖
I need to get to Kristoff. Why?
我去找克里斯托弗 -为什么?
Oh, oh, oh, I know why.
哦，哦，我知道了
There's your act of true love right there,
你的真爱之举就在那里
Riding across the fjords like a Valiant,
像勇士一样穿过海湾
pungent reindeer King! Come on!
辛味驯鹿王! 来吧!
Look out!
当心!
Back this way!
回这边!
We're trapped.
我们被困住了
Slide, Anna.
滑下去 安娜
We made it!
成功了!
Go, Go, Go, Go...
快走...
Come on, buddy, faster.
快呀 老兄
Kristoff!
克里斯托弗!
Sven!
斯文!
Good boy.
乖孩子
Kristoff.
克里斯托弗
Anna!
安娜!
Elsa.
埃尔莎.
You can't run from this!
你逃不出去的!
Just take care of my sister...Your sister?
照顾好我的妹妹 -你的妹妹?
She returned from the mountain weak and cold.
她从山上回来了 又虚弱又寒冷
She said you froze her heart.
她说你冻住了她的心
I tried to save her, but it was too late.
我试着去救她 但是太晚了
Her skin was ice. Her hair turned white...
她的皮肤结冰了 头发变成了白色...
Your sister is dead... because of you.
你的妹妹因为你..死了
No!
不!
Kristoff?
克里斯托弗?
Anna!
安娜!
Elsa?
埃尔莎?
No!
不!
Anna!
安娜!
Oh, Anna... no... no, please no.
安娜.. 不要告诉我你死了..
Anna.
安娜.
Anna?
安娜?
Oh, Elsa.
哦, 埃尔莎.
You sacrificed yourself for me?
你为了我牺牲了自己?
I love you.
我爱你
An act of true love will thaw a frozen heart.
真爱之举可以融化一颗冰封的心
Love... will thaw...
爱..可以融化..
Love... Of course.
爱..当然了
Elsa? Love.
埃尔莎?  爱
I knew you could do it.
我就知道你可以的
Hands down, this is the best day of my life...
毫无疑问 这是我一生最美好的一天
and quite possibly the last.
很可能也是最后一天
Oh, Olaf. Hang on, little guy.
雪宝 坚持住 小家伙
Hey, my own personal flurry.
嘿 我的私人降雪
Anna? But she froze your heart.
安娜? 她不是冻住你的心了吗
The only frozen heart around here is yours.
这里唯一被冻住的心是你的
I will return this scoundrel to his country.
我要把这个无赖赶回他的国家
We shall see what his twelve big
让我们看看他的十二个大哥哥
brothers think of his behavior.
会怎么看待他的行为
Arendelle thanks you, my Lord.
安瑞戴尔感谢你 陛下
This is unacceptable.
这我不接受
I am innocent. I'm a victim of fear.
我是无辜的 我只是一个惊恐的受害者
I've been traumatized. Ow! My neck hurts.
我有精神创伤  喔!我的脖子好痛
Is there a doctor I could... No?
这里有医生吗... -没有?
I demand to see the Queen!
我要求见女王!
I have a message from the Queen.
我有一条来自女王的消息
Arendelle will henceforth and forever
安瑞戴尔从此以后永远不会跟
...no longer do business of any sort
鼬鼠城有任何的
with Weaseltown.
商业来往
Weselton. It's Weselton!
威士顿 是威士顿!
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on! Ow, Okay, Okay...
快来 快来 快来   好的 好的
Pole...Oops. So Sorry.
柱子   哦 对不起
Okay. Okay. Here we are.
好的 好的 我们到了
I owe you a sled.
我欠你一副雪橇
Are you serious?
你认真吗?
Yes. And it's the latest model.
是的 这可是最新款式
No. I can't accept this...
不 我不能收下这个...
You have to. No returns. No exchanges. Queen's orders.
你必须收下 不能还 不能换 这是女王的命令
She's named you the official.
她正式任命你为
Arendelle Ice Master and Deliverer.
安瑞戴尔的冰块总管和运输员
What? That's not a thing...Sure it is.
什么?没这个事吧.. -当然有的
And it even has a cup holder...Do you like it?
甚至还有杯托哦..你喜欢吗?
Like it? I love it...
喜欢? 我爱这个...
I could kiss you!
我真想亲你!
I could. I mean I'd like to. I'd...
我的意思是 我想 我..
may I? We me... I mean, may we?
我能吗?我们 我... 我的意思是 我们可以吗?
Wait, what?
等下 什么?
We may.
我们可以
Summer!
夏天!
Hello.
你好
Are you ready?
准备好了吗?
I like the open gates.
我喜欢打开的门
We are never closing them again.
我们再也不会关上了
What? Oh, Elsa, they're beautiful,
什么? 哦 埃尔莎 它们太美了
but you know I don't ska...
但你知道我不会滑...
Come on, you can do it!
加油 你能行!
Hey, girls!
嘿 姑娘们!
Hey, Guys
嘿 伙计们